One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Thank You, Daddy
Bonney...
Did you see everything?
Yes.
Gee...
I've broken my promise to Kuma.
Whoa...
I'm sorry, Vegapunk!
Give me your hand.
Why?
Kuma entrusted this to me.
It's a present for your tenth birthday.
From Daddy?! Yay!
There.
What a beautiful sapphire!
This necklace looks like the sun!
I'll treasure it!
The sun?
Mm-hm!
The Sun God!
Kuma said it was just a good-luck charm,
but indeed,
who could have imagined two years ago...
that kid would turn into
something like that?
Speaking of which, Straw Hat is
Daddy's best friend's kid, isn't he?
Yes. I was surprised
when you two arrived here together!
Fate works in mysterious ways.
After you went into that room,
so much has happened on Egghead...
I was just saved
by Straw Hat Luffy and his crew.
I'll tell you everything.
Let's join them once you've settled down.
I'm sorry, Bonney.
Sorry that I'm just
a paltry hired scientist.
No.
No!
It's all...
his fault!
Present Day
Egghead, New World
Dammit! Why can't I move?!
Bonney!
What the hell is this?!
I don't know! It might be his power!
Food...
Meat...
Somebody... please...
I wish I could get some for you,
but I can't move...
Reporting in!
we captured Vegapunk's
bodyguard, Sentomaru!
Sentomaru...
Bonney...
Jewelry Bonney, the pirate.
Your father, Kuma...
is dead!
What's the situation?
Anyone below the rank of commodore
can't go in, so we're in the dark...
Can you believe it?
This newly declared Emperor
is now taking a hostage.
Yeah.
It might be impossible for this to end
without bloodshed.
It says the island is
more heavily surrounded than Ohara!
Is he okay?
Straw Hats' Hostage Situation
Dr. Vegapunk?
No!
You're not doing it right.
Keep your hands up like this and...
like this!
Do you understand?
Cool!
One more time! I wanna see it again!
Alright, I guess it can't be helped!
You greedy boys and girls!
This oughta satisfy you!
Oh, what's wrong, Dragon?
If Kuma is being driven by
a fragment of his natural instinct,
where do you think he'd go, Iva?
If it were me, I'd charge Mary Geoise
without a second thought,
but Kuma would not.
I think he'd...
Now why don't you...
go meet your father in the afterlife?
If I'm gonna be killed anyway,
I'll take you down with me!
Distorted Future!
Nika-Like...
Nika?
Future!
Again...
I became weaker again!
Why?!
Of course...
You are his daughter.
So you know that name.
But...
you don't know...
what it is.
What the hell are you talking about?
Apparently, she hasn't made...
the connection between Nika
and Straw Hat's white appearance yet.
What a...
shame!
Hey, who gave him food?!
What?!
N-Not us!
We didn't give him anything!
Put seastone cuffs on him
immediately!
Right away, sir!
On it!
Get him!
Stop it!
This geezer...
I can't even manipulate his age...
Why?
You seem to be wondering
why your power is waning.
Bonney.
That power of yours...
is something I gave you.
What?
It was an experiment.
To see if it was possible to...
give an infant, who couldn't eat
solid fruit, power with a fruit extract.
It was a success,
but the fruit itself is worthless.
Its powers might allow you to
transform into any future...
but the more you know of reality,
the narrower your potential becomes.
You want to believe
Nika is real, don't you?
He is real!
Ever since my father was turned into
a cyborg to serve you,
I've been searching for him,
hoping he'll free my father!
Your weakening is proof that you are
starting to believe Nika is not real.
Your father also believed
in this ridiculous Buccaneer legend,
and said to me...
"I want to save people just like Nika did!"
It was also I who conducted
drug experiments on your mother,
who was the eighth wife of
a fellow in the Holy Land.
But those blue blemishes
showed up again, so it was a failure.
It didn't go well at all, but it was interesting
that the side effect was inherited by her child.
S-Something fell from the sky!
So it was all you...
Your experiment?
It was your experiment?!
Kuma's family...
was tormented by sapphire scales!
He sacrificed himself for it!
How could you offer him a deal
as if you were doing him a favor?!
Come now.
Put yourself in my shoes.
Would you bother yourself
with the feelings of mere insects?
It is inconceivable!
What?
Is it a pacifista?!
N-No!
He has paw pads on his hands!
Don't tell me...
he's the real...
Reporting in!
On the southwestern shore of Egghead,
the former Warlord of the Sea,
Bartholomew Kuma has appeared!
He's advancing towards the island's center!
The authority chip isn't working on him!
We can't stop him!
Kuma came?! Why?!
What's all the fuss about?
Kuma could not possibly be here.
I can't...
I'm too afraid...
to say anything.
Stop him! You're clear to fire!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Daddy...
I feel like I'm falling apart...
Maybe...
Maybe it'll be...
easier...
if I just... die now...
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Oh, this is irritating.
You damn brat.
Shoot her in the head.
– Stop it!
I'm sorry.
Daddy.
After all the effort you made
to save my life...
Daddy!
B...
Bartholomew Kuma!
Impossible!
Why is this happening, Vegapunk?!
He should be... He should be dead!
The Buccaneer boy...
Your lot in life is to be a slave and die.
Your mother's dead...
I think she's better off that way.
Kumachi...!
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry, Kumachi.
I'm dying. It won't be long.
He should be dead!
Because days after
the Revolutionary Army took him,
I pressed...
his self-destruct switch!
St. Saturn!
Curse you...
The town...!
Hey! What?! What's going on?!
Kuma did this?!
H-H-H...
He punched...
one of the Five Elders!
H-H-He's one of
the highest authorities of the world!
A mere slave struck
a man at the pinnacle of the world!
This is an unprecedented atrocity!
Rescue St. Saturn!
He's buried under the collapsed buildings!
I can move!
You're right! Thanks to Kuma!
Bonney! Are you hurt?!
This is our chance!
Take Bonney and let's make our way up!
Escaping is our only objective!
I'll take Kuma!
Wait!
What happened?
I didn't install a self-destruct switch in you.
Because if I turned you into a bomb,
they might use you as a suicide weapon.
But I followed their directions...
by installing in you
a total shutdown switch instead.
Now that it has been pressed,
you should be in a vegetative state,
without will
and unable to even hear commands.
You have no reason to act on,
and it doesn't make any sense that
you came to this island where Bonney is...
scientifically!
So is it true then?
It's not their physical strength
that makes Buccaneer People special.
They once...
It's over...
Kuma.
Where's Straw Hat?!
We couldn't capture him and now he's gone!
How can I report this?!
Thank you, Daddy!
I saw all of your memories.
I'm so happy, Daddy.
Mom was such a wonderful person!
And you wrote me so many letters.
Daddy. That made me really happy.
Even though
everyone calls you a tyrant,
I know you were the kindest
and coolest person in the world!
And I'll never ever forget it!
St. Saturn!
Spider geezer?!
He wasn't dead?!
Hey, Vegapunk!
How do you explain this?
Was it your doing?
I suppose it must look that way.
I could say it was the power of love
if you could believe it.
I see...
Then it's a delusion of humanity
and an error in the human body.
Hey! How come his body is regenerating?!
Farewell. I have no more use
for you people.
Get away, Daddy!
Please move!
Don't make Bonney sad!
Spider geezer!
Kuma helped us, too!
Radical...
Indeed, you guys have grown remarkably.
Beam!
Go to hell already!
Show me...
Franky!
your growth!
Vegapunk!
Daddy isn't moving!
Kuma!
What should I do?!
Atlas, can you carry him to the Labophase?!
Leave it to me!
Atlas, move it!
I'll handle this!
Take care of Bonney and Kuma!
Go!
Are you going to let them go?
I do not care.
Oh boy...
With even Kuma here,
we've got too many important players.
Let's get this over with.
You can't bear it?
You're a sad man, Kizaru.
I mean, Borsalino!
I'm a miserable sight, aren't I?
I should have worn a darker pair of shades.
This is an order.
Impose sanctions on
those who defy the World Government.
The buster call has been invoked!
This island has been designated
as a threat to the World Government.
All ships, prepare to fire!
We'll burn everything down
in the name of justice!
Concentrate fire
and destroy Egghead in its entirety!
Th... The buster call?!
Those who study the secrets of the world.
Those who carry the blood of a lost race.
Those who have awakened an ancient god.
This island...
is full of inconveniences!
Conquering the world, believing in the future
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
What did you see, what did you learn?
nani o mite nani o shitte
Once again, I couldn't save a soul
mata daremo mamorenai no
My fault their voices're fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
Don't even have time to hang my head
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
We're setting off again, my ship!
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the open skies
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
Which is why...
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
Everyday, we can't quit
EVERYDAY makerenai
Everyday, we can't lose
We've got something right here to defend
mamoru mono ga koko ni wa aru
Were my predictions all wrong?
yosou chigai kamo
But I can't stop anymore
tomarenai yo mou
We forge on, sharing the loneliness
kodoku o ima wakeai susumu
Don't chicken out now
ojikezukuna yo
I'm nothing like I used to be
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare ni mo jama dekinai yo
So move!
saa doite
Conquering the world, believing in the future,
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
counting the endless nights
ikutsumo no yoru kazoete
What did you see, what did you learn,
nani o mite nani o shitte
taisetsu na koto ni kizuita no
to realize what's really important?